

Dionísio Braga

💌 dionisiobraga551@gmail.com 💹 +244996754465 👂 Luanda-Kilamba, Angola Luanda





Objective

Front- end developer with more than 2 years of significant contributions, lover of absorbing knowledge and developing technically with the team, person who is not afraid to innovate, with curiosity to try new solutions and technologies, with versatility and thirst for learning, with experience in creating efficient, scalable and affordable solutions. At the same time, I like to share knowledge.

Education

Graduating Oct 2021 - Present

Kilamba Polytechnic, Luanda, Angola

Employment

Front End Internship Feb 2020 - Jul 2020

Mundo Digital, Luanda

HTML, CSS and JavaScript to create responsive landing pages for business and customer.

Junior Front-End Developer (Freelancer) Dec 2020 - Present

Website development for beauty salon and aesthetic treatment, front end made with Html5, Css3 (Bootstrap) and implementation of control with the backend in javascript.

Projects

Order Management System

Techs: Html5-Css3-Is

CDP_Virtual (namely) is a web-system for Order Management for Restaurants.

Learning Platform

Techs: Html5 - Bootstrap4 - JavaScript

Namely as: Netstat, aims to teach programming from scratch to production.

I consent to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of recruitment for the position to which I am applying.

Personal details

Website

Dionísio-Portfolio (johnbraga45.github.io)

LinkedIn Dionísio Braga | LinkedIn

Skills

HTML5

CSS3

JAVASCRIPT (ES6 + OO)

Nodels

REACTJS

BOOSTRAP

GIT

AUTOMATED TESTS (CYPRESS)

Languages

Portuguese

English

Personal Budget

Tech: JavaScript (ES6)

Record user budgets along with the CRUD option.

know More: Orçamento pessoal (johnbraga45.github.io)

Finance Website

Techs: Html5 - Css3

Development of a landing page for a financial website as a study

project,

Know more: Finans - finanças pessoais (johnbraga45.github.io)

Electronic Menu (For Restaurants)

Tech: Php - Bootstrap

Virtual menu with drinks and food section and reserved area for

ordering.

Netflix-Clone

Tech: React.js

Netflix clone using react.js for end-of-study project.

Know More: Netflix (johnbraga45.github.io)

Africell - Site

Techs: Html5 - Bootstrap - Js

Clone of the new telephone operator in Angola. **Know More**: Netflix (johnbraga45.github.io)

Travel Agency

Tech: React.js

Know More: React Router 6 (johnbraga45.github.io)

Courses - Udemy

React + TypeScript

JavaScript

Git

Fullstack Development Present

Skill-----Year

- Html5 3y
- Css3 3y
- JavaScript 2y
- Node.js 1y
- React.js ^1y
- Bootstrap 2y
- Git 2y
- Automated Tests (Cypress) 1y